Hello and welcome back to the section in the section we're going to learn bootstrap in the previous
section we did a bit of a hasty immanency assist we learn how to use styling paddings and the basic
stuff.
But we're going to go to bootstrap now and to begin with what we will do is we will try to use bootstrap
on this space and see the difference because this is this really old school and you don't want to be
real.
So we have such a structure it looks it doesn't look right.
So we can use bootstrap in what would serve itsay has him and his team are CSSA and javascript's framework
for building responsive mobile first projects on the web.
So without further ado let's get started.
First thing you want to do is download books ready to go to get bootstrapped dot com and you can download
bootstrap from there.
And just click the button and download it.
I've downloaded so I'm going to show you from a distance.
Or we can even use the N word.
I think we'll come back to it later she didn't simply means that instead of let me show you just the
previous one it's better you will understand the style set with it here.
So this is how we defined in this small style set.
So this is how you can use bootstrap.
You can download the dirty faces and then you can link to your main page just like this in the head
section and that's all we can do.
But another option is to use CD and it simply means the content delivery network.
And if you use this one you can still use wood.
The thing is you don't need to download bootstrap locally and do all that stuff do it will automatically
work from the CDN and it is pretty good.
It's fast and it's perfect for the web so once you're ready to push it to the production but for development
Poppas it's always good to download and work with that lets down down the download and once you have
that ready we can start using it.
So here in my distro I created a folder called Bootstrap and I have downloaded the answer here.
So let me double click to extract it and I don't need this.
I'm in the mood to try and here in so you can see we have siestas farms and javascript.
It all comes as a bundle with bootstrap and bootstrap has it.
I can say with this glyph icons.
But when I'm going to use that we're going to use front of font or some guidance with the most popular
one and that's the one you see most of the people using So we'll use that.
Let's move it to crest and Zabol screwed.
We need javascript.
And then she says you can see we have many versions where many failed version which is good for production
but you can even use like I said before you can use the CD and so on.
Is this bootstrap would strap dirt insisted on we need we we don't mean.
I mean if I had more trust and let's give the team and that's what they said were more to trust.
So it seems right now we have CIRCE's and we have showpieces and most of the clergy is in those groups
who have the votes of those.
So what I'm going to do now is copy these files and put it here and get rid of this for us.
So we have a folder inside this photo.
He says that was when you were ready to start working on our project so close this
and instead let me drag this folder would send the one I just created and let me remove this folder
from because it was so we had bootstrap folders in default we just showed a system that was downloaded.
And let me create one indexed hosting.
So in the next lesson we will start using bootstrap and what are we going to do is we're going to redo
the site that we did earlier.
This one we're going to use book 7 try to make it beautiful and pull your response as you can see this
is not corresponds to the image gets caught out on the screen gets smaller and all that.
So you we'll all be good with words.
And also in the next next video.
Thank you.