Get started it's let me open up my text editor.
OK so we created index file and here.
So this is our biggest.
Hello world and some stuff let's go with that first we need to degrade Dr.
head and insert head six and it's quite
stra and it's quite boring.
You know we need to link all this see a ceasefire so let's get a link.
So we are going to think here see as his services for seniors is
we'll a policy that says we should be ready to start using will triple-X dried out so would show how
it works is we create the first thing we create is a container div.
It's good idea.
And then inside indeed we created a class called contenta.
This is a strip class.
I'm just making it up.
This is the butcher class and using whatever it it's all about using their their class name.
So they had they had different writers Their them and we used that to argue what are we trying to achieve.
And we can obviously read more about it in official site.
However this discourse prevailed for all that because it can be overwhelming in the beginning.
So you'll be good with me.
And then later on THE NEXT go more obviously.
So the first thing you want to do is clear deal with the container.
So inside this container we will put everything into the world you want first is we need to create a
role for us not to deal with the class of Roe.
And so Roy is like like I'm all the way from right to left.
Now inter-sex that's true.
So inside Roe we might want many sex and we might want one two three many sex and so gay would set rules
are Rose must be be our must have total of 12 Kolb's 12 Quillen.
That's what they call it.
So inside Roe we can create columns we can create one column and give it class name of call them small
talk like that.
So this is the most basic of bootstrap.
You create a can deal with the content.
And then that is really the main content of that whole everything inside this company you'll create
a row and you can have many rows.
So we create the first row and we want to have some content inside there so that our content will have
the full width pro-coal we can't have more than 12 column in one row.
What we can have meaning small columns that really are total to true.
So if you don't want just one column of 12 you can create many but we'll come back to that later.
OK so this is the so called them small tool.
It all worked beautifully for us and on the screen as well.
And later I will show you again that medium and large and I'll show you how that was too.
So to start with.
Let's let's try something here.
Let's ride Hatoum
low or save it and let's try it out let's open this browser.
And as you can see.
Hello world.
Because we are already using bootstrap.
You can see the different the different looks with different ways of bootstrap specific font.
And you can see for batting on the left side and all this.
So we have already used words for.