This let's have a look at all sides.
OK so we had the main text and then we had a bit of a description with the horizontal.
Let's try to recreate the same thing with bootstrap and we will add more later on.
So
let's call her horizontal line and then let's create a better some dummy did not mean text it looks.
See her in the mirror.
Beautiful So as you can see bootstrap is taking place.
It looks around looks much better.
So we created the content seconds and we created a row internal to do with the cause of trub.
What if we want to send to the text we can use obviously we can use this style she has this our own
she says.
But with woodchip it's really all you have to do is because you want to send to this deal the content
of this deal.
You want to center in the square.
So all you do is text the sender even if it is not a text you can use this class name and that will
send to the content of this device say with friends and you can see it's center.
That's how whatsapp works.
It's all about using bootstrap class names to make our life a lot easier and building fully responsive
beautiful web with Bass's are all about giving you the background color just like this.
Let's get you to back up again and bootstrap for that.
It's pretty easy.
Woodchip has a class name it's called jumbotron
and what it does it gives a just like the name Jumbo and it creates a bit of a background with bare
padding with mice and these that are also out for you all these most useful class names.
So don't get overwhelmed don't.
Don't worry.
How are you going to remember all these classes.
Just the ones that I cover in this course will make you pretty much ready to build almost anywhere best.
So once you get busy once you start building a couple of projects you'll be good.
You'll be really comfortable.
So it's not nice to call them truckle grade send the text and then we apply this let's see how it looks.
The first
different that we can we use the spirit of programming Jumbotron for how beautiful it looks.
It's amazing isn't it.
That's the beauty of bootstrap.
So this is how we can see the change as soon as you apply Jumbotron.
Beautiful.
How about making it full with especially on the top of the base.
That look really good.
If we freehand make it full with.
So we didn't do that just by sending the class name again.
So previously I said content but content also we have one more option for that content fluid.
Once your blood contains a fluid what it does is fluids.
It stretches the entire screen.
So let let's try it out for us.
And as you can see it stretches the whole screen looks beautiful now.
All right.
So that's exciting isn't it.
This is beautiful the words were but it's really really fun to work with and makes her life a lot easier
and we can create beautiful pages in no time.
All right.
More in the next lesson.
Peggy.