It's good to be working with bootstrap
the next thing we want to do is you know that's how we use them this year.
I'm another maybe heading to.
And then we'll have the means and maybe we'll have some direction on the one side and image on the other.
So we need to clubs right before on the heading.
We did one call right here we want the half of the square and we went in and another half we on decks.
So how do we do that.
Pretty good.
We'll try to get squared heads to
heads to get this deal.
Let's leave it.
Let's start with another Dave.
So you can feel free to create as many days as it is.
It's pretty good.
It's a good practice like it did and this time also we create a column called small
so we create another deal with the whole world.
And then this time we want to have two six inch two columns.
Right.
Let's create called six then let's create another one.
So what I've done here instead of this deal with the 12 call that is the maximum 12 column allowed again.
So instead of we created six and six.
So it always has to talk to.
OK.
Either way it doesn't render properly if we create one with the six and one with little three.
It would be total 9.
So it doesn't read properly so always make sure you you totally to truck.
You can even create 4 4 4.
So trade deals and in total 12.
So that's how it works.
Always make it to 12 weeks and the first day.
I want to put it in this.
So let me bring
the images to our folder first.
We had used images.
Let's bring this full term currency and we are just one of these images we can use
images.
So would serve has in his class as well for Responsive EMIs.
So it is responsive for that cost.
Obviously we just grid images tight and then we give it a class name of E-Myth response.
That's what Strub glistening.
It make the Lewis-Francis.
Now the source is in Mrs. fooler with the name of the.
You say that we heard the side of an all day let's call it.
E-mail us at recruits
and be mean.
It for us.
And as you can see it's in the hall of the first call which they call them small six beautiful 5:51
and we can write decks with the texture and it is beautifully Pressman's you don't need to worry about
that.
We must have who then say hi to this and say This works perfectly.
It sits inside this deal and just pretty responsive.
I added some text to call them it's good heads to head into it.
There's no way you really are going to learn to make me look beautiful and the words do x.
Like you say read the chapter and verse.
And as you can see we've got the Tardieu and the text you're.