As you can see there's a slight difference because once you apply a Jumbotron it gives a different from
styling and all of this.
And then the normal one looks very different.
So know we can always override this what looks pretty great at the moment that's the benefit of using
too much fun.
So make it stand out.
So that's good.
So we have image we have the text now this in now let's say let's let's imagine that it was web based
forums.
Travel Agent or travel site or something like that so maybe we want to show something is a button that
says Book.
Book 2 or something like that.
How do you do that.
It's it's pretty straightforward with words so it's really easy to create beautiful buttons.
Let me show you one.
We have a paragraph and after this paragraph let's say we only queried about some bottom up.
We are always open and close the bottom to the button and then said Here let's get to class without
class them let's have a look at it
too.
So this is how it looks without class any class.
And this is already using words so it doesn't look this good as it doesn't look that good.
But let's play some would show us
let's give it a class name of button always you actually start with button and then button dust's primary
and there are many different classes in there.
They have I think six class names they call primary danger that has a red color.
That's danger.
Another one is sukses.
Another one is there are quite a lot.
We can have a look at them.
One prominent one such info and their stuff like that we can come back to it later.
Let's let's these folks in this modern primary.
Let's have a look how it looks for first.
And as you can see spiritually as well Joe Johns is learning.
And that looks beautiful.
Organ.
So this far it's looking good.
Let's let's continue this one.
The next thing let's create some lists.
What to do it because I'm all human small screen.
I'm going to collapse this as soon as I can see the whole way and see this.
He's clicking this arrow and it collapses again.
So we have the mindif contained a fluid inside that we are working with this inside this row.
Great.
Another day.
And let's create do clone more
and we want to create some list dives right.
Ordered lists.
Page three Weren't you the most memorable takes center here.
Some creation.
So at least we do know the list you know and then that would serve as a class name for this class list
group
and waiting list would call you of interest group.
Right.
And so yeah.
So it started with a list group and then group item.
So want to get it straight after after a while you'd be comfortable with this.
And let's create some
looks the first and you can see the list is rendered beautifully how good it looks.
Let's make it a bit more interesting.
Let's make it.
All I wanna do is I don't want it destroyed all the way from here to here from right to left.
I want it to be somewhere in the Middle East here in the center.
So how do you do that.
Let me say we have to deal with the code taking the full with trust.
So instead of what I can do is I can put all these elements inside another column.
Let's copy that so that we can this.
Let's create some divs Let's create call them.
In fact I would say easily.
OK.
So we had we have these we'll call them grid.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to use only six.
And what about the rest of the six because we have to always make it to work.
So what are you going to do is call them small or set free.
Now what this really do is it will take the six call and then the rest of the both the right and left
side it will offset three.
So on the right three on the left three it will offset.
So right 3 and three six plus six.
So that's how it works so now that our content will be centralized center in the middle and it will
have the offshoot columns 3 and 3 on both side.
So we are as you can see here this side of offered 3 3 kobun this side of it in the middle six column
and it is taking place we the.
So this is how you can use both circuits really form and we can do a lot more.
We're going to be very creative with this.
So we'll do more with bootstrap in the next video.
Thank you.