Or let's continue with farms would farms are one of the best features of the woodshed.
It's really easy to work with forms.
So what are you going to do is let's create some forms and submit
it so we have this div let's collapse this as well let's quit.
Did you.
The
paint as an asset to
farms in Bootstrap.
It's creative.
To name some form of control that's a bootstrap class inside.
Instead we created.
You form with a class name form control.
And we created did we get a last name of form group and instead of let's call it
name that we call the let's call it the and then field text
class will the form control.
So we created we didn't need to do with any.
We just create a form and then inside form we create a DB.
The first DB will have in full field of in-fill filled with the type of text and it will have a label
called names so people understand what it's about.
Let's do the same.
It's copy and paste mean email Prosor.
You go to
I
got the last word don't last for.
And finally let's create I'M BORED BORED BORED.
For all those you named some literary
looks pretty good.
So we have fun and people can fill in the name.
E-mail us or as you can see we are Blagden Embassador so it doesn't it obviously.
So it has and then comes name and possibly comes and submit.
No it looks a bit odd.
That's because wasn't in full.
Now let's try it here.
That's prober.
So this is how it looks.
Looks pretty good.
Prom's in Butcher really easy and beautiful.
How about the one we did here.
We have the radio button checkbox.
Let's try them out too.
Let's do that.
Let's do the same.
So let's create another deep.
We don't need the input fill in soon to have them here label and then we will put you in put.
Type
said.
It's you name so names should be in the label.
This is just the input field name we can call it what are we going to call it.
It's going to be
one.
So people are going to say this is the same for worry about
you
and me
Ray.
So this is how easy it is to work with friends in books.
And now we can give a different class name to buttons.
We can give
success and looks different.
We already tried primary here so is and begin doing x ray.
And that's that's how it works.
We learn how to create a function which is pretty cool.
And we do more stuff in the next lesson.