In this lesson I want to show you how we can study using foreign awesome icons.
They are the most popular eigenstate and they really really change the way your web site looks.
It's really important going to be very creative with those arguments.
Let's get them in this time I'm going to use CD and people but I didn't use Sirian but this time I will
use and so you know how to use that too.
So sing songs for CD.
We can download it onto their site.
And so you want them to is the site
you can download and link the same way we did with butcher.
Are you can to sit in let me use the N
and copy this for farmers.
But she is copy
expensive.
Nobody should have to use.
Let's try let's try.
So this is our first deal.
You.
This is a first day.
Let's put right after this.
I want to create a deal with a treat called Groote just to see.
So after the first did they quit and quit and deal with Colomb small.
And inside this deal I create a 3D with 4 4 4 4 4 inch deep comb.
Paul
let's call it.
So is Dave let's say let's let's put some I can for sure that we can see.
Let's good to find awesome.
So Ian I was going from here ording.
I'm going to do is good icons on top and then I can certify it and instead of looking at it and then
it is to do some research.
Let's let's put some like like this.
This is like any good.
It's these absence.
Let's try this time.
Clicking this one and you can see fit to use this we have to use this class name for fun.
Awesome.
A sense of fun.
Awesome awesome desk.
Thumbs up to that.
And is it too soon to copy that.
And then we want to put it in this dibber.
So let's play it here.
And let's let's take another one.
Another one word works.
Let's say it's one of these let's say infl
fool.
There are nine
How about first sir.
What is this.
Info let's see is this
Corbie could.
And in the second do you.
Yeah let's try one more let's try this.
Travis
these I consumed all of you really.
And here they get you.
OK.
Now that's good for us and see we've got the Titans.
Beautiful.
Now let's use our custom styling to make them look awesome.
Let's make them bigger.
Give them color things like that.
Let's do that.
So we need to first need to create our style.
Right.
We don't have our styles idiot.
We are only using bootstrap.
So let's let's do that let's do that in the next list.
Thank you.