LET'S MAKE IT WAS AMAZING using these I can show you how you can do that.
First thing let's let's put them inside the Jumbotron.
So this deal that we are working with these icons.
Let's give you the class name of the jumbotron and let's create a custom class that's for our use.
OK.
I can I can I can.
So this is this has a class in all of them will turn.
And then we have given a different class name as well which we will use later to customize savey.
Yes.
It has got the Jumbotron but we wanted to change the background color and do a bit of styling.
So for that.
Well I wouldn't do it.
It's always good if we can apply some CIRCE's and see live.
See the action you know take effect live.
So for that there's a great plug in.
If you're using Google Chrome and I'll show that that's really useful.
You sirs for live see is in your
is one of the Cormac's since you're there is I had this in so just wanted to show you.
That's right.
I could do it again.
I just simply add to Chrome I extends and as you can see here this is the one we're working.
Now what we can do is we know this Jumbotron has a class name of items right.
This is the one I give the counseling.
So let's let's use this and let's let's try this here please allow access to file.
You are.
Come on.
I love it.
These things can be a bit annoying sometimes.
All right that's great.
So we have all I can see you.
Let's play some studying so and I can swear.
OK.
And then let's let's apply some styling and see see it happening real quick.
Background color.
That's right.
I want to take color pick an extremely crude
color didn't want blue being a
maybe light maybe some sort of like background color.
Look at that.
It's beautiful isn't it.
All right that's good.
I can actually lead them on.
All right.
Let's try this again now the problem is it's it's you know I want a bit of a margin here.
How do you do that.
A margin top maybe 20 bucks.
Let's make it 50.
That's good.
And as you can see by default bootstrap has all these bar boards really radius these things.
And I want it to be completely rectangular and or not like that.
So you can do that.
You can remove that by using radios in general.
So
Budarin radius or tournaments with bootstrap is that it's a default to the behavior you need to overwrite.
Sometimes you can do that is using this important thing.
So as soon as you apply the important as you can see this Baldrige issue will be gone.
As you continue to do this with services keep in mind you.
So we have beautiful.
Now let's make these items bigger.