All of them it starts with fire.
And I can I'm going to use this for the moment but you can always give it a unique class name if you
want to you know or by the individual because it will be easier later on because I try to do it or be
lazy and do it again.
My I go that's them and like them my work.
This is the Kostner see.
So all of these icons have the same class in my icon.
And now I'm going to apply the styling to my I can apply to all these items with this class name.
And later if we create more class and we want to have the same effect we can simply apply this in that
that's it.
So let's try that.
So this one we're going to copy paste you know later and now let's try this.
I can in here let's give them a bigger bigger size and size 50 piece.
I think you need to save this file for us and then rephrase this please.
So just so that I don't lose this competition.
This is Furr's history.
And as you can see as soon as our blog says it says beautiful 50 pictures that looks good this could
be Sewanee or you can do this in not center.
So let's let's make it Center.
And that's pretty easy we would sir.
We can do this syndrome with the text.
So the whole deal is centered on the content.
Corporatists are going to lose it for as you can see its center as soon as I applied this thing.
It is Saenger beautiful.
OK so the next thing is now we're going to copy this.
She this is put in our style.
So it is really easy to do it live right.
This is a great blog and copy this is.
And we're going to put it in our own studies.
Now I think we don't have one yet.
Head style bootstrap would serve we don't have our let's create our link and head Tref Let's create
my Sternbergh see it says.
It's clear to insert these nice timers you find
we.
And based on that we tried earlier say we should press and beautiful.
So that's how we learn how to use front on some items and we learn how to use our own system.
Awesome.
All right.
So we'll do more in the next lesson.
Thank you very much.