This and I will see how you can use with some navigation menu bar on top.
So it's good to bootstrap with the official side.
And so just search for both navigation and let's go to the site and let's go to dokes.
To.
Let's use this this navigation has everything forms drubbed everything.
And we will remove the good nature.
This is the complete code.
Sits inside that tag and then it has a contained a fluid.
It has a deal with all these bars which is simply the hamburger menu when the menu gets more from mobile
devices.
And then we have the desex and all the links the and the writer of the net by all these links Let's
go over this and break it down.
Groby
And right after the board is done let's proceed.
The first thing let's let's save it and see how it looks.
And friends and there is it's looks pretty good.
We didn't need this from let's get rid of that.
So where is that from that.
That is it is six.
Yeah.
And this from where the name is let's remove these.
And let's keep only this I really really want this.
Well some of the
who this leftside job done let's get rid of it.
It's good to have it again.
You know these links I want links to be here.
Let's fix that up.
So what we have here is obviously we started our navigation here.
Never said that this is the next day in day.
Most important one from the biggest one is how to use this.
And then this is using the night class and it's the default.
Never.
We can't even send this to the universe and then the universe will look like this black default will
look white.
Let's keep it like again.
So the next thing.
So this is I showed you this works for the mobile screen like as you go inside and go smaller as you
can see the the menu collapses and becomes hamburger menu.
That's that's Teigen that that's for those I can sample.
These ones are going to let's leave them there.
And then there's another dig this deep has honored at least this one.
We didn't want this on this on the left side.
So let's get rid of that.
So we have that on our list and it has lists you first list and second list in your second list has
a drop down.
So inside this list has many other things to like.
This is the first list this one has one link.
And then again another on our list starts.
It is a drop down menu and then it has all these options.
Save it and see how it works.
So we have the link.
We have just done.
And then we have one let's get dropped on that we wouldn't really want them.
However I would take some of these links Cobi.
And then let's remove this from let's move on and let's keep it simple let's just keep some things and
we'll make them clickable.
OK so this is the for the hamburger menu.
Little icons look three lines.
And this is the the usual one when this new service or brand in this next house.
So let's let's repeat this thing and it's been made of or and probably are making small should.
Well in the screen.
OK so we started with the navigation bar.
We give them a class name of inversed and we have first dibs again this deal contains everything you
see is cynicism.
Right before the knife so this container fluid fluid because it is stretching all the way from right
to left.
So that's there and inside that deal we have this deal.
This deal is mainly for this I can.
The collapse I can get to so that's that that's that's good.
And then the many all we have is this it's this this is how you can leave comments in his team.
I think so it's pretty straightforward.
Let me show you this exclamation mark does this.
And then there's those clues.
So in-between everything you write will be discarded and it will have no effect in the code.
Again
this is our bootstrap mania.
Your navigation do this header with items and then mentally.
This is where we have to deal with the collapse Nabat collapse.
And this is the idea which responds to this city.
It sent this idea and this is and that's how it works when it goes to the small screen size.
That's how it works.
And then we have these links on our list we created and then we have the following things link.
And then about
services.
All right.
Looks like we are in one of them.
So we have to fix bigger bedding here and then and then let's make it responsive.
So we have this button.
But if it doesn't work and we'll fix that to that's do today.
So we have to link that as well so I will show you how to do that in the next list.
So I hope it is pretty straightforward to understand.
So of course only this month.
Now you read was a lot with my son and this makes the navigation.