So we have our menu which looks pretty good but the problem is when we make it small it looks good but
when we click it doesn't work.
So how do we fix that.
For that to work we need to include javascript which haven't included yet.
So what you have is when we downard would serve obviously we got the days folder and inside this folder
we have bootstrap the data is all we can use manufacturers.
So we have to link to one of these and we can.
We need to use Indic query as well.
So let me hard decide what I'm going to do is all these scripts put it right before the end of the body
so that the page renders pretty well.
And then the script or otherwise it will delay the learning process of the base.
So always keep it right before the end of the body type of a script.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to use the include the script for booths for
these service is.
So Sanjay is less mature.
Yes.
Yes that's right.
And we are in a crucial period that we can get that degree is meaningful.
Let's take the minute that was in the
here
and you can do the same for Bush.
So you can include from Sealion but since we have always done let's use that word is easy to use from
the scene.
It's pretty good.
It's fast for folks inside as well.
Let's let's see if it works for us.
Let's use from Syria and so they agree.
And so we are using both from Syria and latest compile and in hindsight was Kovi was probably an Egan
day.
All these so you don't even have to worry world.
But let's try this again sir.
So we included the query from the CDC and we included bootstrap javascript also from the official side
city.
And we put it right before our task.
Now let's try if it works for us.
Small and beautiful works beautifully.
That's awesome.
That is what we can do next.
Let's actually let's treat this styling.
The one we had here this one so let's switch to ZDF and see how it works.
Remember that
for some we are already using machine that's fine.
And the only local stylesheet is this hour my style and everything we use from the CD.
I mean let's try to dig more with the team.
I think that's the
it's
head Six looks a bit messy but it's not going to be worth it just the links for she didn't from the
officials.
Now friends.
All right.
Yeah.
Everything looks perfectly beautiful.
Now one more thing I want to fix is I really like these curved curved thing here.
I want to make it straight.
Let's let's do that.
So this is obviously the nab right.
It's kinsman's solids tarradiddle.
So I'm sure you are you comfortable with this navigation right.
The secret here is the detail that the secret here is how this hamburger menu this will item.
How does it represent the the actual man.
How does it know.
That's the thing.
That's how it does is.
And he's into this deal.
We have this button and all these lines for a second third.
These are just the lines.
If you remove that save it and go and the first is lower.
So it just the line I can you.
So these ones they are inside this button and this button has the data toggle class and another target
and the target is this thing.
But for example number collapsed.
And that is exactly the same I.D..
Remember this hash tag we use for ID and this data we use for class processes.
So this button with this spend Marsch it's targeting the actual navigation which is this which is in
this deep.
And as you can see beares example net net collapse one.
And here is exactly the same.
So this is how it works.
This bottom how it how that's how it goes to control this one.
For simplicity let's say let's say in many senses is can gift you have made carbon copy and start again.
So let's send this to him Logan fix this border radius and let's fry them in live here.
This is pretty cool.
Border radios are a big.
It's Corbie this thing and let's put it inside our systems.