OK so let's make these links clickable.
All right.
So you clicking Contact I want to reach to desex and contact you get them services may be destroyed
or services or things arguments.
So not index file didn't you collapse this.
So the first thing you want to do is let's fix this contact from where it click on the contact form.
We want to get to this.
So let's send these two up on deck.
And then let's this contact from this whole thing is inside this room.
All right.
So let's get this wrong idea let's give you the idea of contact.
Right.
So if you do just this like this is being called a deadline.
So if you do that this is good for testing when you're developing.
So when you do this today as we get to the same position as the skeletons.
So we come back to the same place and nothing happens.
Instead we going to use compter to the ID when people click on this link.
The reference is it can be like I saw the URL it can be some of those sites you know things like that
but in our case it does the idea of contact.
So once this is clicked on we're looking for a device with the idea of contact.
And if we find here
this way you get the idea of context and that's how it works.
Say it could reverse the biz and if you click will be taken straight to contact for you isn't it.
You can even give these takes to pass how you do that legs so the earlier buttons they have Button button
primary button danger but shucks has been in for all that.
And they're different colors so you can use the same format here.
You can say text instead of button primary you say text from here you know and see that the primer the
send button call you got this same color here.
We're going to use this to make it capsular but I'm seeing the hard coded numbers simply
weren't there.
And I said
you're
horizontal you are I really like present my simple and elegant beautiful.
All right.
So contact for me got.