Want to make it through to be able to use the Google ordinary Go for it.
Yes.
Let's open up our folder.
We have used this and this open with something in the world because the word we used in has to be so
cool.
So I'm going to finally get it right now.
It's in Birdie's
head had.
So we got this phone to use Barina.
Now let's go right here and that's.
That has to do is make heads and heads do goods give them the Marine
said.
That's just.
It doesn't look that great but pretty cool.
What we can do is let's make them
I want to make them bigger and we can even use inline style.
Sometimes it's really handy in case I'm like now we can use this bring it down.
Read.
So let's add in started they form
form search
on sizes maybe 50 books.
Make a nice big beautiful Gondek 456
or this.
That's me.
All one has to fit it.
We get one size fits.
Just give them the color and sort of thing what that all that we can take some interesting code with
try this.
This Inori.