You it's going to come in like this column see how beautiful it is.
It's not that bright.
That's right.
So let's see if we call it it's.
What is the actual name.
So you can do that by going to inspect and then normally when you have when you hold her away you can
see that this content is active and you know this is EC2.
And then they cut and again however she talks currently where we are in the right place.
This is the call I really like with this Kwabena.
So that's how we get these girls to handle
get through this and they should have the send this one does reason.
And there were
extremely it's
not all going to be awkward.
Sometimes it happens with words.
So even though it's clear the new class is.
I to make it even bigger.
Well that's good.
All right so this is how it is we have this man text.
Yeah.
We have this.
We have.
We have six and we have ordered list on wordless contact from Awesome.
OK so we were actually going to open the link again we did.
And now what do we have we have this let's make it let's make it so we C6 here.
You know
Mrs.
reunion is totally because it's so services offensive but even the point
and is so it lives over.
Let's give you the idea that he would go back to the menu.
So first we need to get to the content and services we get to the services.
And when you scroll over as you have noticed the menu disappears we can keep it always on top.
We can do that by just going to a menu.
It that it was never fixed.
Don't.
That's the classic.
No.
It always stays on don't you.
All right.
Contact me in the contact room services when the service is about or.
Let's make this six in about right.
These is this a good idea.
And Bob
All right.
Which services the men been good about this about services contact.
Or is it this case and learn how to have links to our menu.
And we did a bit of a sighting do and we'll do more in the next list.
Thank you.