Are to going to use tables it's really easy to use tables and bootstrap
after the contact form.
Dig deep.
It's.
Common.
It's good idea to come and come to you to come back later on and you know not to get confused
to
do this.
The men do.
So did you know
do 10
do to
maybe do some
creative
terms to do and then heading heading What do you want.
In the.
That's for the heading that's create a boarded up team.
Devil did the roof.
So wrong.
It was same as the Butcher roll all the way from right to left and then columns.
So this one is 0 and headings did.
So I mean it skewed one
image in one and
the contact index
string.
Mr..
Yeah.
There you have it.
It's what can we do to make it better.
When you say those are terrible I don't believe betting it's that good.
And let's clear some more data to let go of it versus
fresh.
Yes.
Got some data this year with a background background Jumbotron.
And my question is it for Lance to contain Jim Butler was beer
good.
Yeah that looks good.
It's a bit of a bad thing to do.
It would be devil.
This is my last network.
It's different from
my entire picture.
Really easy and beautiful to wait tables in extra.
I get so good that we got there and we got there getting things done.
We created a little
crap table for it.
Are we nearly done with the book.
So we did quite a lot of things.
What are some cool things I want to show you like adding full with background images.
And probably I want to show you how you can apply the gradient color very background not just the solid
and looks really amazing and you will see in the future lessons.
Thank you.