I guess I'll say it is looking really good.
And we have a lot of we cover a lot of things aren't really wonderful things.
It's called panels and they're really cool and released lists we did at least we did so let the bands.
They are really cool.
And then and then we go from there.
And people that just want to say one thing sometimes you must have noticed the sun takes like Count
ball in how they do that and we discover that insects and to so I keep forgetting that.
Let me say so let's go with sex and so this is how the world is this year.
And let's say I want to highlight some of the text and it's good for Search Engine Optimization too
not just for looks good and it works well.
For the broadest search engine says.
So let's say when we ring the bell somebody we need to highlight.
So what we can do is we can use the strong to strong currency and that's me strong.
And then they go and you put the text inside.
So this makes the text board.
See the textbook we can achieve the same effect using B.
We didn't really use it.
I haven't really seen this drag being used.
We get the same effect but Haubegger strong is recommended for Search Engine Optimization that is really
good.
And here let me show you this.
When you use it all the text text gets it that.
And there is one more thing in the registry and there it is the real problem and you will always use
this term there.
So just keep that in mind strong.
And sometimes we can create a blank course as well.
Blockquote
you before I forget to say the
this is the program but let's say I want to highlight this bit of text as a block quote I get to come
and see.
Let me clear this b c you could never put anything inside this blockquote again.
See what happens.
It doesn't look really good in things because we were central to that text.
But
it doesn't that good
it again so one thing someday.
Thankfully.
So did you.
I was a bit forgetting that for you let me create a new deal at the end.
Do you
an do contain B or
you didn't copy paste this.
Oh that's probably because I'm wrapping it inside.
P let me wrap it and said this is do this the better for the better.
Now this is also the program.
However this is a book called
purity from see that these are words.
So sometimes it really gives the dynamics that is needed to your articles and it's really cool.
All right so this is how you can create blockquote is just cool.
So we cover strong tracks and block art and design and our core.
I was going to cost them something else and that's when we had the panels panels.
Excellent.
Thank you.