Let me quickly show you how you can create panels it's really good.
One of my favorite reason to go to the end of our documentary.
It's great.
Believe they can turn you into an intern.
I want to make sure it
does and then I will create three columns.
Column.
As for and
dear in this column I will create a deal with a class name.
Did you then did the board start heading inside this pen with a class name of default.
I would create 3:6 and three days heading body and for I guess it did.
In the deep
and then
Cruger or to deep panel heading let's say hate you
mean the body
threads and then you let's work
your lips
on so see how it looks looks good.
The reason doesn't look that good for this time is heading to me.
Let's use his three because we used to many different ways to and from the get go.
Looks more realistic.
All right or just go to the heading panel footer that's where the bottom button Bartonville Frist and
you can see that's cool.
So this how you going to quit.
So this is the first pen let me copy this plan.
This is called small one copy.
That looks beautiful and you can add icons here on the side.
You can do a lot of things.
The one we did use the food is this this is great.
Using icons really really gives the dynamics for our context of importance and you can quickly certain
juggling decks using the command.
If you follow the rules then these Kunbi
and that's it.
Damn
the first thing I collapsed early and here in this bottom you can it's been done.
So it's more readable.
You can add the button.
I can be far more in the Friends Big
B is my can we in that class.
That should come back here.
So that's how you can customize and make the cost you can use that.
First for the items and you can use whatever things you don't have to homes.
In his bottom muskeg from his work.
So nice to see the difference now.
It looks pretty good.
I guess so.
It's a bit of a pattern for this.
David looks to cause DVD current in a fluid and
my
name doesn't conflict.
DAVID
I don't know let's try it.
Let's try this my balance.
And then I betting 50 bucks or so and 60.
So it's really good.
You can see my copy.
This now to be here.
All right.
So this is how we can work with the books.
It's amazing.
You can see we have navigation we have Jumbotron We have immense restaurants everything is restaurants.
Beautiful.
Awesome.
Again it's looking very good.
Use this blog we use the strong day and night.
I keep emphasizing this summer I didn't want to miss that again.
The tables we got to actually get right are things you are.
We have friends awesome buttons again so we need nearly there.
The next thing I'm going to do is the last thing and cool thing there is also how to use Aquarians.
So your drummer turns you look awesome and I will also show you how to use the bagong e-mails for your
JumboTron is full with.
All right.
So that's that's coming next.
Thank you very much.