Either.
We're going back to bootstrap to yet another video.
And so far we did quite a lot.
We have beautiful navigation.
We have the images.
Recently we did a bit of a I can box kind of thing.
We have the list contact forms.
And there are a lot more components you can use and you can always visit bootstrap and learn more about
them.
But basically we going to go almost everything we did quite a lot.
And so of the cool stuff I'm going to Carwin in two upcoming videos such as in this video I'm going
to cover how you can use scrolls spy.
So what does that is.
When we scroll like this is the services space in his basement but that's what it is.
And this is a contact.
So when he's calling what if we want to highlight this segment like if we are in the services sector
we want to highlight this and if we are in the contact six in our contact link and we want to highlight
this link.
So how do we do that.
And know we can do that using scrolls 5 and that is super easy.
So that's one of the amazing things.
So search for treasure
scrolls by
and we can go to official site or we can even go to those three schools there are quite a lot of useful
examples.
And you know you can always come here for reference.
Pretty good list for that.
And as you can see you can you can try it.
Select the section one and just scroll it goes 6 and B and so on and so on.
So how do we do that.
It's pretty let's.
This is the examples of people trying to in order to have here
is this special class that I Spy and the name scrawled.
And what does it target this one targets the number.
So we have the navigation with the class name of nav bar.
OK.
So as long as we have this class name for the navigation and inside this navigation we should have the
buildings obviously represent all the links that we want to have is great and that is all we need is
this bit of code that a spy school and that's target the name of the number is number.
So look let's copy it isn't
like two days.
And as you can see at the moment it's suppressed nothing's happening.
Doesn't matter where we are nothing's said.
Let's try.
So we're in our index corts DIMA all we need to do is you know our body into the body don't we need
to.
It's not a spike.
Scroll down to target number.
So we have a number we targeting these navigation class.
So it automatically digs in with a page whichever deep we are on equal.
So good typical first as you can see we are in the context of
writing about where in the about when the services were in the country and as we scroll and see the
it does seem pretty good right.
See the last deal.
The names for that the
date from and we don't have any link we can create another link for this one as if we want to lately.
So this is how you can implement this beautiful feature.
Cool right.
OK let's do some more cool stuff in the next video.
Thank you.