Again so one thing we're going to do with book 7 that is adding Karev so carelessly is the image slider
which is really popular these days.
People see a lot of words as hair on top of the page in the landing base.
The image is lighter which is really cool and it's really easy to implement that with bootstrap.
Let's go up soles for boots for our cars.
Let's go to the other side.
Kirsten Temperley boots from
this is how it looks.
So we have the the button we can have some takes some paragraphs and descriptions and we have these
items pretty cool.
So this is the carousel and beggar obviously we can have images instead of this blank thing.
So how do we implement that.
Because sometimes all you have to do to get things like this and this is not just for bootstrap on the
Internet you can see certain things in many different websites and you might want to implement the same
same feature same functionality.
How do you do that.
Most of the time you can simply do that by you know applying the same CIRCE's scripts same styling where
they would use.
So how do you do that by just right clicking and pusilla pays Pacer's.
And as you can see the whole biz is generated by these code again.
So the carousel begins here on the top with just the navigation navigation navigation.
So after that they have Carrousel.
So this is what we are interested in and simply we can copy this code on this copy does and of course
of course it is
and here.
Right after the navigation navigation and this carousel
again.
And so
they've now landed just like
quite a lot but I'll explain pretty pretty straight forward.
So it begins with the DB.
It doesn't deal with it we give it a class name of Carousel carousel and then slide so it does slide.
And Dr. Hardcastle the default class name defaults name for this dog.
And they have active state.
They have the images and it sends it's lived for the moment and the man heading and some description
can always override this one to shoot you need.
And then there is a button with important private plans and yet the mental images are there.
This is the image.
This is this third image is
and so on and this is the I can use they use the cliff I can but we're going to use Formosan instead.
You really change that.
And this is pretty much it.
Let's start with some images but before that let's have a look at save it and have a look in our site.
It looks you don't see it.
David
probably will need to get the census as well.
Let's go to the door.
They always have the you know the headsets and they have this you have yet carousel that she has they
have.
So let's let's get this entire series in or modify it.
You copy and it's going to tell us uses that space.
We don't need all these things on Bombo size of Carousel cartilages.
Let's see this.
Let's listen.
Three zoos
sell hives fixed to 500.
That's good.
But we didn't intend that.
We have our own.
Let's get this
so customized by six and we just deleted and the Kerrison let's leave it.
So get us a base class.
There are some serious issues with Disney Aircel item.
Email is they're doing all the hard work marketing content with this.
We can get rid of it.
That is for the entire business that we saw early on to implement some of those kids obviously feel
free to do that.
Features as you know alternate is that Kerrison thing.
Let's play it for a moment.
Two threads and as you can see we have the Council of biddable.
We need to fix this bit of a padding Otherwise it looks pretty neat.