Write it even for a second slide book
the
browse gallery for every second you're going to have different customized buttons and all the stuff
which is great.
That's good.
Let's go ahead and replace the images.
So we have the images here.
I have downloaded some images.
I will make the whole folder of ideas here you.
So if you want to play and obviously can do source
images the programs should be easy to use.
The next images
source.
Let's do it on the first.
And this time let's use didn't need to.
It is a beautiful lake in Nepal.
It is the next room.
Next is let's use the app.
And meet this man.
So feel free to customize the text on the bottom and all the info we just did the images
you're
this is on top of our page.
Looks beautiful.
That's awesome.
Again.
You can customize the text buttons and all that just great.
This freaks this bit of reading here.
What does the name of calmness mean for you.
Dave is my Kerrison we can begin use carrousel closeness.
Let's try to live curso Mars in bottom a piece of glass.
That's good.
Ken it was and so it's.
That's awesome.
Mike Scott it is.
It's good to see isn't and at this.
MARTIN So Miles and Burton do we have carrots and celery.
No.
Know we have that and it's called
margin bottom six they already applied.
So we applied let's make it simpler.
Austin what I want to make this land different especially in the course of a week or two doesn't apply.
So let's let's face that too.
It's good to be heading let's go to the class of Cairo so getting him
M.S. And let's apply the same class to all the headings
and Curson hating again cruller quite well looks pretty good actually.
The Sterling
interest because there we have it it's beautiful.
So this is how you can use words for as you can see you can achieve almost any lay out any any design
with such simplicity it's incredible.
Something happened here.
We don't need this 6N Let's get for the feature with all the feature and feature it is coming from here.
When we carpet this vision and this space has all the features things so this that styling is so obvious
here.
So one thing I noticed too is that it is the color was built or written and that was because they stenciled
with carpet.
It had this glass it was targeting the entire body section so a new jury.
So this is all we have.
This is all our own starting in the one we copied from there.
That's all on the carousel once we keep and everything else I delete it.
So I said Captain and everything with the carousel we need I get this feature.
We don't even need to and this is the last one we created by ourselves.
So just this one two three four five.
So these five was so silent you keep.
And secondly I could say with the first and looks of it it's looking really good.
And this is it for this listen I'll show you some of cool stuff.
And the next one.
Thank you very much.