So said is look awesome.
Let's add a 5:56 in as well in the food in the closing of our contained inside this.
Let's create the same as the inadvertence of a word.
And then that's right.
Copyright.
And if you were to read copyrights and you can do and you you're being way copyright
in your
freezer word conservative to where I think you get this character is on top of you should enter key
on your key word or phrase.
And there we have it.
And as you can see the copy or the copyright I can that looks like that.
So there are some special characters you have to write like this and all is well how to write code how
to write a certain characteristic you might need to know and that you can quickly search and Google
can get things done.
So footer Let's hope it is let's put them aside.
Deal with the class.
Richard in
this footer.
This is for the his team and Michael this is for the standard.
We are following for Search Engine Optimization and this division just for the design this is for to
get the bootstrap design.
However this is the actual His In a market that is necessary for the proper housing base.
So you always put further nonfinite finish Legation and all that stuff.
But the rest of it all the deals.
They're just all styling bubbles.
Let's let's use the Jumbotron glass looks pretty good.
JIM
Yeah that looks beautiful.
That's very good for future also.
We did quite a lot.
What else we can do with future is just so good I just can't stop me.
Feel like doing more and more let's do this.
Art subregional I want to add a background image.
Obviously we have vision but this is a slider.
But I want to show you why and how to use the background fully with background images and on top of
that we will have probably services that so I'll show you that how you can do it in the next video.
Thank you.