Hokus let's add a background image for with a fixed background image to start with this section.
So the first thing that's good to our services.
DB The one that may collapse this one.
This one is blockquote.
Let me collapse this as well.
And this is the table that collapsed this
this is from
and this is the services.
This is normally interested in working.
So
it has that idea of services like.
So let's use this idea.
We don't need all these guys who can use ideas will submit.
Let's use the copy
and let's try it so we can use this because we use the data with ID has services.
And what we want to do is in this deal with the class name ID name services we want to use the background
image.
So there is a serious class for using background images which is as you go Simmons's background color
is back on Amy's background.
And then we supply the you again your parenthesis.
And inside we give the address in double quotation marks.
So let's do that for you don't you.
Insert image is.
And there is a beautiful
right.
That's good.
Some more images.
Yeah I was not sure I know it looks no.
No it's
cute it's it's
so it is taking just enough space for this content.
If you have bigger more content it looks great.
So this is all we want at the moment.
It looks actually pretty good with this deep blue it and slowly and light.
It's good.
What I'm going to do is reduce the margin so that it's going to act as it's designed by a margin of
two or three beats
and there's 20 for tonight.
And that's 30 over
that salute beautiful.
And we can also give a thing so that when you scrub the image stays fixed.
And when you scroll up and down it gives kind of a very nice effect as if the content is moving whereas
image is not.
So let's hope it does.
And let's make it fixed.
You know you see Zunes
see heads
and you know as you can see when I'm scrolling to the background stays the same only the content changes
her that that's awesome.
Let's make it bigger.
Let's make this the
506.
That's beautiful.
On to or play some she's just 36 and has two different suits in the middle.
It looks pretty neat.
Pretty good.
Now we're focusing the images very well.
That's Austin de the content.
Let's give this.
So this is the one retargeting But this device which holds all the content lets you read a class name
its last name of
content.
So I was just going to see the score with this one so that it could be you know scissors.
And then the one we just created is this will be this one first.
And as you can see it means it's not there something you have Also what are done here as you can see
that there is a bit of a building on top and bottom and this text is center.
So I see that using these services.
So let me actually copy this
in without this.
It looks like this as we saw it earlier but as soon as you apply this this is as you can see how black
the bally on top and bottom.
You can even write like this reading it right up right left.
You can even do this.
So it applies on top and bottom and then the second same thing is for the right and left right and left
as I to leave it there as it is.
So this will this is this we have the center content of the applied bit of betting top and bottom and
Geraint right and left and we got these styling which is as in the bag on e-mails.
There was one issue which I fixed and I think my wriggling was of that time.
So I just want to show you how to fix that when I move.
That is why I was using there live.
It was working fine but as soon as I move it didn't work.
So if I leave it just like this let me just say that before we were trying like this right.
So if you go first as you'll see the image is gone.
That's because when you actually play it and CIRCE's stylesheet what happens is it has to follow by
a domain.
So it in NHL website when you push whoosh out to the live show you'll have the domain name.
And then there will be a full name.
So you'll have my domain dot com Sless images.
So there's no way in all that but because we work locally and this is the actual path we need the index
obviously but this is the destination of our for that route.
So this is the one I copy and paste here.
So on the user I pull that up to the bootstrap which is the form and then Emacs's and then then does
just fix that up and then you should be glad to the.
Everything is already.
So this is it for this lesson.
Show you one more thing in terms of design and background with images and all this stuff I would say
one would think that is adding the gradient background which is awesome.
So probably will head black to slowly fading to work in the next video.
Thank you very much.