OK I'm sure you're having a great time.
Practical bootstrap again and all these things you learn you can apply it to real life.
And this is this is what you need to know.
We give the slider good background in all this scrolling effect.
Now that you can see the grading slowly goes from dark black to fade and fading away like that looks
really awesome.
You can see such background with gradient if it looks really fantastic.
So how do you achieve that.
Let's let's use the slogan slightly faded car looks awesome let me see the view pencil's actually let's
see the inspect.
And as you can see done with some.
I give it a class name of what you want.
And this is what I use Lynagh brilliant.
Right.
So let me just copy this
Corbin's and then come back to my site and you can get that where it says is creating.
This is very true.
Just by Googling and born here they have pretty good example.
See you see all these actually were done reason looks pretty good.
But for the table I think black and white looks fine.
So you can see all these and they have different styling applied so that it works works well for the
old browsers for Firefox for us or for him.
So if he encounters some problem in Mozambique and hopefully other browsers will support but if not
there's a fix.
So as you can see with we'll throw it away with all this but on nearly all passengers sometimes this
happens some browser works well some eyebrows done.
So what it does is does work it does.
This is falsified.
And everything else is same as a linear gradient.
All this everything is same but for specific browsers there are certain name on up with this new standard.
Hopefully you will have to this it's quite a headache.
This is for Safari Wickett all they use for opera modes they use for Mozilla Firefox and so hopefully
I don't have to do all this yet.
So these Divx which give you the name of it and then add another Gerns gradient.
You know in his first news biz It was then that he
guess because we use words on its head and back.
Ms.
Klans instead here and we have the table from Austin so we can use this to the table.
So
from us so as you can see we can add background radian background which is pretty cool.
You just want to say call up.
I don't have a problem with this.
This is code which is slightly x x x x y
and
word said danger
or nodes straight.
That's awesome.
This is this is just to say use the phrase Buderim
making great.