Are going to be starting decree I want to show you what an absolutely amazing thing that it is.
We'll start out I really love it.
This is amazing.
It's good to well and good with the schools that they have.
As you can see Greek to open more when you click in something like that pops up.
Cool right.
It's let's let's use this Curtiz.
Let's go have a look at the code.
So what they have here is pretty standard here.
They have a tag they have a deal and this deal has this button.
This button gives the data total model and data target is the model the same as we did earlier with
navigation and all that.
So the same way.
So we have a deal with a model with the idea of class Fred and then we have the two different divs with
buttons one has for closing and then we have the header we have the body six.
And we have the button.
It's pretty standard.
So let's take these example and try it out.
Gourley starts here.
And then let's go with the compre
scorpion is also quite a skill in.
Which is really helpful.
And nothing wrong with that.
Everyone does the same thing because you can use
the Sablon plugin for that without one for you without them.
So they didn't have to always go there and Kope you can generate things kind of like let's say bootstrap
3.
And as you can see it get all the the mark up.
However I will say the next how will you do this but for the moment let's say that in say it and that's
how it is at the end moral example open and open up how good is that.
That's awesome.
All right.
So let's let's make it Center in lets make sense to modern Hedger like Zandu.
All right let's leave it let's keep it a double.
This is
a lot of copy based here but I'm sure you got the point.
It is necessary are you patient.
There's a better way would say next but there's no point in writing line by line.
It's just a lot of time and saved lives.
And as you can see we have the model.
It's a bit of a digital and we can a better.
What is the name of this model.
DB It's called Murder box.
This
50 piece.
Called
it first and that was all right.
So we can use this we can use this to create Let's say we can even pull this contact from inside the
murder.
So you can simply say contact us.
And then when people click on the Contact Us they will get this contact.
That would be awesome right.
So you can be creative and do a lot of stuff.
And let's see what we would be doing in the future once we get into degree.
Maybe we'll do some things with this model or maybe not.
Let's see but as you can see this is really cool.
OK so let's let's wrap it up let's wrap this with subsects.
We learn quite a lot and I hope you really enjoyed it and then definitely again we're amazing were business
responsive fluorescent spaces and bootstrapped you once you have reached this far and practice a few
times and I'm sure you love practicing because it's honest fun.
It's so much fun.
All right.
Thank you very much.
And I will meet in the next six and with Dick Gregory.
Thank you.